162 Estcourt Road Fulham, London SW6 7HD 02073818544 | 07894714690 joelerickson@hotmail.co.uk

JOEL ERICKSON PAYUMO

PERSONAL STATEMENT

Over 10 years of Management experience in Hospitality, Retail and Administrative duties. Company start up experience and excellent people management skills. Advanced computer skills. Adaptable, Dependable and organised team player with the ability to communicate effectively and efficiently. I work well under pressure and love challenges.

SKILLS

Management | Business operations | Finance | Administration | Organization | Planning and events Staff management | Social media and marketing | Art and Design | HTML | Microsoft Office Google Drive | Maintenance (Handyman) | Cafe Barista

WORK HISTORY

FLAGSHIP ASSISTANT HOTEL MANAGER, TRAVELODGE HOTELS

June 2017 - Present

DIRECTOR/ OPERATIONS MANAGER, BREW BOX BUBBLETEA

December 2012 - December 2016

MAINTENANCE MANAGER, KEYSTONE HOSTEL

October 2014 – July 2015

GENERAL MANAGER, WILLIM HILL ORGANISATION

April 2009 – March 2013

CUSTOMER ADVISOR, THE NUTRI CENTRE

November 2006 – November 2007

EDUCATION

GCSE, ST ALOYSIUS' COLLEGE, 1995 - 2000

Business and Economics C, English BC, French D, Geography C, Mathematics C Religious Studies C, Science (Double Award) BB

GCE A LEVELS, SIR GEORGE MONOUX COLLEGE, 2000 - 2003

Business Studies D, General Studies C, ICT D

INTERESTS

Web Development | Stock trading | Buying and selling | Technology | Food and Drink | Art and design Photography | Sports and Fitness | Travelling